Mr. Sukhrob Ilyosbekov

Age: 21

Nationality: Uzbekistan

Email address: suxrobGM@gmail.com
Web: http://www.suxrobgm.net

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/suxrobgm LinkedIn: https://www.facebook.com/suxrobgm

GitHub: https://github.com/suxrobGM



Profile

Thinking "out of the box" to provide software-based solutions

Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills. Expert in C#, .NET, and T-SQL with database analysis and design. Skilled in developing business plans, requirements specifications, user documentation, and architectural systems research. Strong written and verbal communications.

Software skills include:

- Languages: C#, C/C++, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, XML, SQL, Lua
- Databases: MS SQL, PostgreSQL, Access, MySQL
- Software: Visual Studio, Rider, DataGrip, Visual Studio Code, DotPeek
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Coding, testing and fixing programming errors.
- Collaborate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

Work experience

Freelancer.com

Freelance Software Developer

02/2019 – present

- Web Designing and Web Development.
- Worked closely with client to provide a customized website for their business.
- Design and development of various websites.
- Designing and maintaining front end for web and mobile applications.
- Writing unit tests to improve code predictability and documentation.
- Develop support tools to reduce working time from hours to minutes.
- Used coding methods in specific programming languages to initiate and improve program execution and functionality.

EC Dev Team • Uzbekistan

Team Lead

07/2016 - 02/2019

- Managing developers team
- Designing game Al logic
- Programming game mechanics
- Scripting game map
- Programming developers tools
- Balancing game's difficulty.
- Watching on process developing game in a team.
- Ability of enhance and optimize data for match with many devices.

Education

INTI International University & Colleges Kuala-Lumpur • Malaysia

Computer Science

08/2019 - present

• American Degree Transfer Program

Tashkent University of Information Technologies Samarkand • Uzbekistan

Software engineering

09/2017 - 06/2019

• Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Awards

Top-10 team in IT Universities contest in Uzbekistan Tashkent University of Information Technologies

02/2018

 My team was in the list of top 10 teams in contest between IT Universities in Uzbekistan

1st place in Individual ACM ICPC format contest Tashkent University of Information Technologies

12/2017

Winner in individual ACM ICPC format contest between TUIT students

Strengths

Ability to learn from mistakes • Creative thinking • Confident • Critical thinking • Working quickly • Accuracy • Solving complex problems

Skills

C#

Programming Languages

C/C++

Python

JavaScript

TypeScript

Java

PHP ■■□□□

HTML/CSS

SQL **BBBB**

Lua ■■□□□

Frameworks & Technologies

.NET

ASP.NET ■■■■■

WPF

Xamarin.Forms ■■■■□

React ■■■□□

Qt ■■□□

Unity 3D

ML.NET ■■□□□

Entity Framework

Unit Testing ■■■□

Bootstrap 4

Git **EEEE**

ADO.NET ■■■□

jQuery ■■■■

Publications

Introducing .NET 5

http://www.suxrobgm.net/Blog/Introducing-NET-5

05/2019

Introduction to Microsft's new technology .NET 5

ML.NET - Machine Learning for .NET

http://www.suxrobgm.net/Blog/Announcing-ML.NET

05/2019

At Finally! Microsoft announced ML.NET 1.0

Certificates

Certified Scrum Master - Agile Alliance

License 544689

2016

Open Source

Github - contributions in project Server Side Analytics https://github.com/matteofabbri/ServerSideAnalytics

Stackoverflow - reputation 15000+ top 3%